原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译   千只鹤飞过波千鸟  tong大梨  AlgerDestiny
翻译   A序列  五天  马丁马丁回音山  Reece
翻译   Sheersmith  Steve  Pemberton
校对     屯栗子
时间轴     兜兜兜爹
后期     渔夫
总监     屯栗子
辛普森一家
第三十一季  第十六集
巴仔在看医生
常青台742号
请评价行程
小费
不给
这也就是为什么你去法国那座小镇
And that's why, if you go to that little town in France,
这个人无法忍受
牛奶
大豆
小麦
今天的音乐
可以看到我投降的雕像
there's a statue of me surrendering.
我会带你去见巴顿
瞧见没
See?
天哪爷爷  你今天的故事太酷了
Wow, Grampa, your stories are really cool today.
是的  疗养院终于不给我吃安慰剂
Yeah, the nursing home finally stopped using me as the placebo
给了我真的药
and gave me real meds.
但我今天真正想做的是给你这个
But what I really wanted to do today was to give you this,
美国军队
我最珍贵的东西
my most precious possession.
快打开吧
Open it.
如果拔了保险  五秒内就会爆炸
It'll explode in just five seconds if you pull the pin.
都怪我健忘
Uh-oh. Senior moment!
快放回去  放回去
Put it back! Put it back!
不是这么操作的  这就像生小孩一样
It don't work that way! It's like having a kid!
-祈祷吧臭小子  -不要
- Say your prayers, boy. - Never!
骗到你了
Ha, ha! I pranked ya.
爷爷  这真的太绝了
Grampa, that was hilarious.
我完全理解你可能会回答不
I understand if the answer's no,
但我可以借您哑弹一用吗
but can I borrow your dud grenade?
瞧瞧  他睡着了
Aw, he's asleep.
也就是他答应了
That means yes.
春田退休老人之家
今年我们被评为全州
This year, we've just been named the most sedentary school
动员大会
健身也快乐
-坐的最久的学校  -好棒
- in the state. - Yay!
挤不进门的胖小孩
好棒
Yay!
不不不  坐的久是一件不好的事情
No. No, no. Sedentary is a bad thing.
动员大会
健身也快乐
我们的词汇成绩也是最差的
Our vocabulary score was also abysmal.
-这是不是一件不好的  -是的  不好的事情
- Is that a bad... - It's a bad thing, yes.
-好棒  -现在为了让你们这帮小孩
- Yay! - Now to get you kids
站起来动起来  我们决定
up on your feet, we decided to have
用两小时的静坐集会取代休息
a two-hour-long sit-down assembly instead of recess.
不公平
No fair!
-坐下  -是  女士
- Sit down. - Yes... ma'am.
首先  让我们欢迎新的吉祥物
To kick things off, please welcome the new mascot
来自镇级半业余曲棍球队  秃鹰维尼
from the town's semi-amateur hockey team, Vinnie the Vulture.
孩子们好
Hey, kids.
苗浩斯  你没告诉我你老爸又找了份坏工作
Milhouse, you didn't tell me your dad got another bad job.
其实吧  他是候补
Actually, he's the understudy.
原来的人得了带状疱疹
The main guy got shingles.
我的鹰嘴里有蜜蜂
Ugh, there's a bee in my beak!
喘口气  讨厌
Okay, taking a break. Ow!
一个人能被扎多少下呢
How many-- ow! How many stingers can one be have?!
不如玩玩你比划我猜吧
How about a little show-and-tell?
我先来
I'll go first!
不用担心
Don't worry.
这是真的手榴弹
It is a live grenade,
但是只要你不把拉环拉出来就不会爆炸
but it won't go off as long as you don't pull the pin out.
完蛋了
Caramba!
爬进我屁股里来  儿子
Climb in my ass hatch, son.
只是一个玩笑而已
It was all just a joke.
你真是个禽兽  你让我相信
You monster. You had me finally believing
学校终于要被毁掉了  你又夺走了我的幻想
the school would be destroyed, and you took it away.
我也觉得不好笑  巴仔
I didn't think it was funny either, Bart.
你完全不知道我爬进去了多深
You have no idea how far up in there I went.
妈妈  你是听说有紧急事件才来的吗
Mom, you heard there was an emergency and you came?
其实我就是在外面过了个夜
Oh, well, actually, I was just having a sleepover
和那位  小胡子叔叔一起
with your uncle... moustache over there.
妈妈
Mom,
你保证过再也不会喝多了来学校的
you promised you'd never show up at school drunk again.
我不打算撒谎  我处在羞愧的旋涡当中
I'm not gonna lie, I am in a shame spiral,
和下层人鬼混在一起
hanging out with lowlifes and bums.
你好啊  加利
Hey, Gary.
封口费  别再说我的名字
This is to not say my name.
发薪日
Payday!
内尔森  我去你的柜子里打个盹
Nelson, I'm gonna go take a nap in your locker.
自由了
Freedom!
你逼的这位男士跳到手雷上
Son, you forced this man to jump on the grenade
下一秒我都要跳上去了
seconds before I was going to.
辛普森  多谢你了
Well, Simpson, thanks to you,
现在没有人能把手榴弹带到学校里了
now no one can bring grenades to school.
这一次  你会被开除  再也回不来了
This time, you will be expelled, never to return.
求你们不要开除他
Please don't expel him.
他没别的地方可去
He's got nowhere to go.
巴仔·辛普森  我在此宣布你...
Bart Simpson, I hereby declare you...
等等  我住在这个孩子隔壁好多年了
Wait. I've lived next to this boy for years.
他的内心还是善良的  放学之后我来辅导他吧
There's good in him. Let me work with him after school.
我会用三个原则来提高他
I'll improve him with the three P's:
坚持  祈祷  坚持祈祷
persistence, prayer and persistent prayer.
天啊  你是这种人
Oh, God, you're one of those.
-主啊  -别下跪  别下跪
- Dear Lord... - Don't kneel. Don't kneel!
我们这是公立学校  看在上帝的份上
We're in a public school, for God's sake!
发生宗教问题击碎玻璃
恩格尔诉维塔尔案  1962年
"Engel v. Vitale, 1962.
最高法院称
The Supreme Court asserts that..."
丘督学
Superintendent,
你即将被祈祷链上所有人针对
you are about to be on the business end of a prayer chain.
作为政府运作的宗教项目的一部分
"As a part of a religious program carried on by government,
祈祷群
这是历史的问题
it is a matter of history..."
我对祈祷的热爱反应在我的胸毛上
My love of prayer is reflected in my chest hair.
我好像加错群聊了
I appear to be in the wrong group chat.
纽约的上诉被法院驳回
"and the judgment of the Court of Appeals of New York is reversed,
而驳回理由...
and the cause of..."
阿门
Amen.
先生  我们这里有205位经过认证的祷告者
Sir, we're up to 205 verified pray-ers.
祈祷群
祷告之塔
你真想让我把你的办公室地址告诉他们吗
Do you really want me to give them your office number?
丘督学
是吗  是吗
Hmm? Hmm?
丘督学
春田小学
好了  不要  我受够了
Fine. Stop, please! I've had enough.
我们不会开除巴仔
We won't expel Bart.
谢谢  谢谢  谢谢
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
如果你来看管孩子的话
If you supervise this boy,
让他离这个害人精爸爸远一点
keeping him away from the baleful presence of his father.
太好了  皆大欢喜
Woo-hoo! Win-win!
下午好  巴仔
Bon après-midi, Bart.
当你需要特殊照顾的时候
While you get some special help,
我加入了法语俱乐部
I'm hanging with the French club.
别用法语取笑我就好
Well, just don't make fun of me in French.
你这个笨蛋
Vous êtes un imbécile.
祝你和弗兰德斯有个愉快的一天
Profitez de votre journée avec le Flanders!
明天见
A demain.
我们要去野餐
Ah, nous allons faire un pique-nique.
闭嘴  闭嘴吧
Oh! Shut up. Shut up!
你不会讲法语吗
Vous ne parlez pas français?
这很好  不是吗
Isn't it great, son?
洗碗既可以做家务也能冥想
Washing dishes can be both a chore and a meditation.
我的内心确实平静了一些
I do feel kind of at peace.
不好  割到手了
Uh-oh. Cut myself.
天呐  天呐
Oh, my God, oh, my God!
逗你玩
Gotcha!
我能把这个变成真的血  小混球
I can make that real blood, you little punk.
你刚才说什么
What did you say?
我刚才的意思是
What I meant to say was,
你的这种态度嘟嘟嘟会改变的
oodily-doodily, we'll change that atti-toodily.
钓鱼
Fishing?
一种增强注意力的药品
我还没有服用利他林呢
When I didn't take a Ritalin?
-你太残忍了  -别说了
- You monster. - Hush.
你如果什么都没钓到  我们今晚就没东西吃
If you don't catch something, we don't eat tonight.
愚蠢的垂钓
Stupid fishing.
愚蠢的平静
Stupid peace and quiet.
愚蠢的日落
Stupid sunset.
这里绚丽多彩
Thinks it has so many colors.
非常的美丽  金光灿烂
So beautiful and bright and golden and...
看看你的鱼竿  巴仔  鱼咬钩了
Mind your line, Bart. You got a nibble.
我抓到了  抓到了
I've got it! I've got it!
我亲手杀了一条鱼
I murdered a fish. Me, by myself.
别太骄傲  孩子
Don't get cocky, son.
你还要清理一下鱼然后吃掉
You've still got to clean it and eat it.
首先  我们要生火
First things first, we got to start a fire.
用什么生火
Uh, with what?
我们自己动手来成就自我
We'll build character by building it ourselves.
该你了
Your turn.
我手好疼
Oh, my hands hurt.
我们是有童工法的
There are child labor laws, you know.
这是最笨蛋的
This is the most idiotic...
-你感觉如何  -很好  为什么会这样
- How do you feel? - Great. But why?
这就叫做成就感  孩子
Well, it's called "Accomplishment", Son--
是一个靠你自己努力赢得的
something you've earned yourself
别人夺不走的东西
that can never be taken from you.
左撇子握手
Left-handed handshake.
既然你现在已步入正轨
And now that you're on your way,
没人知道你还能多优秀
there's no telling how far you'll go.
*奇异恩典*
*Amazing grace*
*何等甘甜*
*How sweet the sound... *
我的天呐
Oh, my goodness.
我们的儿子从来不会那样唱歌
Our little boy could never sing like that before.
我觉得他唱的不怎么好
Well, if you ask me, he's not doing so well now.
令人惊讶
Mm. Remarkable.
我以为让巴仔变成小天使的唯一办法
I thought the only way to turn Bart into a little angel
是弄断水上乐园的电线
was a downed power line at a water park.
你一定很自豪
Ah, you must be so proud.
你成功让那孩子改邪归正了
You really turned that boy around.
过奖了
Oh. Well...
恭喜你
Congratulations,
内德·弗兰德斯
Ned Flanders.
做的好  弗兰德斯
Yeah. Way to go there, Flanders.
你太棒了  内德
You the man, Ned.
你们不能把所有的功劳都归于他
Hey, you can't give him all the credit.
是我们先把他教坏的
We're the ones who messed him up in the first place.
听着  愚蠢的弗兰德斯
Uh, listen, stupid Flanders,
我是来表达谢意的
I just want to say thank you,
要是有什么我能帮上忙的...
and if there's anything I can do for you...
首先  你可以不要再叫我
Well, for starters, you could stop calling me
愚蠢的弗兰德斯
"Stupid Flanders."
开始了开始了
Oh, here we go.
不  就这一条
No, that's it.
谢谢  弗兰德斯
Thank you, Flanders.
没那么难吧
Was that so hard?
他正在胡子后面偷笑呢
He was laughing under that mustache.
你们在这里干嘛
What are you doing here?
巴仔在做数学作业
Bart's actually doing math homework.
我想亲眼看看
I wanted to see it for myself.
等一下下
Bup-up-up-up!
听着  我能辅导我自己的孩子
Listen, I can help my own kid.
我想想看
Uh, let's see.
四又三分之二加六分之五等于
Four and two-thirds plus five-sixths equals,
算一算
uh, uh, carry the math...
然后...
And, uh...
惨了  作业被狗吃掉了
Oh, no! The dog ate it!
问题不大  我已经做完了
It's okay, Dad. I finished it.
在弗兰德斯先生的帮助下
With Mr. Flanders' help.
看起来我没什么用处了
Well, it looks like I'm useless.
让我带着最后一点尊严离去吧
Let me just walk away with my dignity.
又肥又没用
*我还能向谁求助*
*Who can I turn to*
沮丧黛百货公司
[原为布鲁明黛百货公司]
*当没人再需要我*
*When nobody needs me*
我的儿子不爱我
My son doesn't love me.
[西语]你现在很难过  但你的儿子是欣赏你的
等他长大了  他会懂得尊重你
你根本没听懂我说了啥
You don't get me at all.
春田垃圾场
逗留了五万只海鸥  不会错的
孩子  我也很伤心
Hey, kid. I'm sad, too.
你不应该一个人在这里
You shouldn't be out here alone.
没人在乎我
Oh, nobody cares.
爸爸离开了
My dad left.
妈妈是个酒鬼
My mom's a drunk.
我住在拖车里  轮胎都是瘪的
My house is a trailer, and all the wheels are flat.
我最后一口干粮是一块冰块
My last solid food was an ice cube.
我的电视是装着一只松鼠的牛奶箱
My TV is a milk crate with a squirrel in it.
这孩子真惨
This kid is such a wreck,
连我都有资格帮他
even I could help him.
还能借此机会报复巴仔
Which I could use to get back at Bart.
该理发时我就躲在灌木丛后
I get my hair cut by hiding in the bushes
等修剪的园丁来
when the gardener comes by.
我要去做吗
Am I gonna do it?
利用一个孩子的感情去伤害
Is it wrong to take advantage of one child's feelings
另一个孩子  有错吗
to make another child feel bad?
没人知道答案
Nobody has the answer to that.
孩子  我来帮你
Here, son. Let me help.
好了好了  擦擦吧
Okay, okay. Enough snot.
孩子  你想不想要个导师
Say, uh, listen, kid, how would you like a mentor?
导师是什么
What's a mentor?
就是一种特殊的老师
A mentor is a special kind of teacher.
但你啥都不会
But you don't know nothing.
我能教你的多着呢
Hey, there's lots I can teach you.
如何偷走派里的馅
How to steal filling from a pie.
怎样不用流血就能得到饼干
How to get cookies without giving blood.
用薄荷口香糖怎么除臭
How to use spearmint gum as a deodorant.
也许我还会带你去看牙医
And maybe I'll get someone to fix your teeth.
竟然存在只看牙的医生吗
There's a doctor for your teeth?
你能教我这迷宫怎么走吗
Can you teach me how to do this maze?
咱俩一块研究研究
Well, it'll be a project we can work on together.
酷
Cool.
等我一下  我没番茄酱了
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm out of ketchup.
我抄完
I'll give it back
就还你
when I'm done.
巴仔
Hello, Bart.
跟你说一声我要去内尔森家了
Just wanted you to know I'm going to Nelson's house.
我俩很亲密  非常亲密
We're close. Super close.
首先爸爸  你打给了我
First of all, Dad, you called me.
其次你给内尔森做导师
And second, are you mentoring Nelson
就为了报复巴仔吗
just to get back at Bart?
才不是
No! No way!
但你要碰到巴仔记得给他看照片
But if you happen to see Bart, show him these.
发件人  爸爸
四张图片  下载
孩子  我打算教你收拾行李的速招
Okay, kid, I'm gonna teach you how to pack
适用于你老婆要把你赶出家门时
for when your wife kicks you out of the house.
衣服都扔到前院吗
Are the clothes thrown out onto the front yard?
先假设你有时间去拿个行李箱
Well, let's say you have enough time to get a suitcase.
什么是行李箱
What's a suitcase?
好吧  咱教点别的
Uh, all right, let's move on to something else.
但我得先问你  你跟我妈睡过吗
Okay, but first I got to ask: Are you sleeping with my mom?!
没有
No.
你是第一个说这话的人
No one's ever said that!
这就是我们的蓝图  孩子们
That's what we're going for, boys.
不敢相信我们竟是骄傲巡游中的一员
I can't believe we're gonna be in the pride parade.
基督教徒的骄傲
Christian pride.
基督教徒终于可以公开展示信仰了
Finally, Christians can openly show our faith.
我们确定  我们纯洁
We're sure! We're pure!
习惯就好
Get used to it!
巴仔
Hey, Bart.
快看我教会谁骑车了
Look who I taught how to ride a bike.
内尔森本来就会骑车
Nelson already knew how to ride a bike.
对  但他不会发出酷炫的摩托车的声音
Yeah, but he didn't know how to make cool motorcycle noises.
我来帮你骑上去
Uh, let me help you back on your hog.
我和内尔森可亲了  大家都叫我们"侯默森"
Me and Nelson are so close, people are calling us "Homeson."
侯默森出发
Homeson away!
侯默森
Homeson!
妈  你看见没有
Mom, are you seeing all this?
-看见了  -你要做什么吗
- Yes. - Are you gonna do anything?
-不做  -为什么
- No. - Why not?
这次情况很复杂
This is a complicated one.
两个男孩都受到了帮助
Both boys are being helped.
我要说的是  该给阿麦换衣服了
What I'm trying to say is it's time to change Maggie.
你在哪里  我的小借口
Where are you, my little excuse?
抱歉
Sorry!
爸  你到底在教内尔森什么
Dad, what exactly are you teaching Nelson?
存钱入户
Banking.
瞄准成功
Aiming for success.
打入音乐圈
And breaking into the music industry.
给你40块
Here's $40.
对我来说不是小钱
That's a lot of money to me.
但我希望你能做个疗程看看你做的事
But I want you to get some therapy about what you're doing.
40块钱的疗程这就来
40 bucks' worth of therapy coming up.
我说的是持证理疗师
From a licensed therapist.
老谋子的确有贩酒执照
Moe has a liquor license.
对  我们就别讨论这个了
Yeah, let's not discuss that too much.
钱拿去  吃点药
Take the money. Get some help.
你干嘛这么做
Why are you doing this?
爸  我必须充当道德之声
Dad, I have to be the voice of morality.
才不是
No, you don't.
我很喜欢当道德之声
Well, I like being the voice of morality.
我很喜欢相信这角色没有限定我人设
And I like believing this role has not typecast me!
我还是可以演莎翁作品的
I can still do Shakespeare!
发光的未必都是美味达福液体金
All that glitters is not delicious Duff Gold!
原梗出自《威尼斯商人》所引用俗语
尿尿还是憋死
To pee or not to pee!
原梗出自《哈姆雷特》
To be or not to be, that's a question.
这毫无疑问
There is no question!
不
Oh, no!
抱歉  我得尿尿去
Excuse me. Got to pee.
疗程或尾气检查
两者都不用  可免费停车
医生  我现在都明白了
Doc, I see it all so clearly now.
我害怕成功是因为我父亲从来没时间陪我
I'm afraid of success because my father never had time for me.
-意味着  -时间到
- Which means... - Time's up.
-再说两分钟  -没什么突破
- But two more minutes... - It's not a breakthrough.
现在我比来的时候感觉还糟
Ah, now I feel worse than when I came in.
下个月见
See you next month.
好了  40块你能说十分钟  开始
Okay. 40 bucks gets you ten minutes. Go!
我想让自家儿子嫉妒  就去辅导别的孩子
I was mentoring another kid to make my son jealous,
然后发生了奇怪的事
and something weird happened.
我真的喜欢上那小东西了
I'm actually starting to like the little dingus.
帮帮我
Help me.
我真是惊恐万分
I am appalled!
只因为你那可怜的自尊心
You are ruining two boys' lives
就去毁掉两个男孩的生活
for your own petty ego.
让我告诉你优秀的心理医生会怎么说
Let me tell you what a good therapist says.
他们会说  "你做什么都是对的"
A good therapist says, "Whatever you do is right"!
对有钱人才那么说
That's only if you're rich.
导师来啦
Mentor entering!
侯默小甜心
Hey, Homer, honey.
来跟妈妈温存一会
Come on, spend a minute with Mama.
听着女士  我可没兴趣...
Look, lady, I'm not interested in...
-什么鬼  -我懂你的
- What the...? - I know.
你跟我儿子在一起
You're just spending time with my son
只是为了让你儿子嫉妒
to make your son jealous.
迟早你会离开他的  就像其他人一样
Sooner or later, you're gonna leave him, like all the rest.
那会让他心碎的
And it'll break his heart.
我又不是来拯救世界的
Hey, I'm not here to save the world.
我只是个导师  来了就教  教完就走
I'm a mentor. I come in, I ment, then I go.
把真相告诉他
Tell that boy the truth.
孩子  我们得谈谈
Son, we need to talk.
不  不要  我知道结局会怎么样
No. No. I know where this goes.
谈到最后你扔下个555开头的电话号码
It ends with you giving me a phone number
转身就走了
that starts with 555.
不  等等
No! Wait!
你还有什么可说的
What do you have to say?
我教导你
I was only mentoring you
只是为了惩罚我儿子变得如此优秀
to punish my son for becoming a better boy.
-我就知道  -你要去哪
- I knew it! - Where are you going?
我要去报复你  留不下你的人
I'm gonna get even. I can't make you stay,
我就去找你的孩子撒气
but I can take it out on your kid.
别害巴仔  我真心爱他
Not Bart! I do love him!
报复屋
学徒的复仇
啊哈哈哈
基督徒骄傲游行
提示  骄傲是罪孽
我们是基督徒  我们骄傲
We're Christians! We're proud!
但别大声嚷嚷
But don't say it too loud.
手拉着手传递神的旨意
Holding hands are holy hands.
真恶心  你抹护手霜了吗
Ew. Are you wearing lotion?
我的手干裂了
I'm very chappy.
纯洁的牧师
面包和鱼[谋求私利]      算命半仙
投票给上帝和昆毕镇长
祈祷之手
游行高潮
投票给上帝和昆毕镇长
欢迎各位基督徒
Uh, welcome, er, uh, Christians.
上帝愿感谢我们的合作赞助人
God is pleased to thank our corporate sponsor,
查·蒙哥马利·伯恩斯
C. Montgomery Burns.
你怎么不去死呢
Why won't you die?
伯恩斯先生稍后会回答问题
Mr. Burns will take questions later.
多亏这次壮丽的游行
Er, uh, thanks to this magnificent parade,
你们这些右翼蠢货会让我永远连任
you right-wing ding-dongs will keep me in office forever.
犹太人爱耶稣        无神论行不通
现在到了这华丽游行的精彩高潮
And now, at the spectacular culmination of the parade,
投票给上帝和昆毕镇长
随着最后一辆彩车驶过终点
when the final float has safely cleared the route,
一双巨大的祈祷之手
a giant pair of praying hands
会从街道两旁合十
will swing from the sides of the street
殉道者打地鼠
构成神圣的祈祷之姿
and come together in holy union.
犹太人爱耶稣        无神论行不通
祈祷之手
游行高潮
他想挤死巴仔
He's gonna crush Bart!
弗兰德斯去哪了
Where's Flanders now?
我在这  你有啥事
Right here. What do you need?
离我远点
Get away from me!
气球荆棘王冠
非基督徒科学监测
医生可通过病症检测信仰
不要啊
No...!
你好爸爸
Hi, Dad.
儿子  一起乘救护车吗
Son, you want to ride in the ambulance together?
好啊  这可是咱俩的老传统了
Aw. That's always been our thing.
-爸爸  -怎么了儿子
- Dad? - Yes, son?
能让我吸一口氧气吗
Can I have a hit off your oxygen?
当然
Of course.
我真是个好爸爸
I'm a great dad.
本集结束
不好
这集太短了
很抱歉利用了你  你是个善良的小孩
I'm sorry I was using you. You're a sweet kid.
总有一天我们会喝着酒回忆今天的蠢事
One day we'll have a beer about this and laugh.
-明天就喝怎么样  -可以
- Can it be tomorrow? - Sure.
但今天  我要给你介绍一位愚蠢的
But for today, I know a certain stupid someone
但是比我更懂得做父亲的人
who might be a little better at this than me.
-有什么心事  孩子  -说了你也不懂
- What's the matter, son? - Ah, you wouldn't understand.
你这种富有的教堂迎宾员不会懂
A rich church usher like you.
我自己家也有两个捣蛋鬼
Hey, I got two troublemakers of my own.
谁让你俩打扫这个垃圾场的
Who told you boys you could clean up this dump?
没有人
No one.
我觉得我会理解你的感受
I think I just might understand how you feel.
你失去了父亲  我失去了两位弗兰德斯夫人
You lost a dad. I lost two Mrs. Flanderses.
或许我和我的儿子可以带你一起去看比赛
Maybe my boys and I could take you to a ball game sometime.
-你意下如何  -好爸爸
- What do you say? - Papa!
好棒  我们有哥哥了
Yay! We have a brother!
野蛮的收养哥哥
Mean foster brother.
上帝保佑罗德和托德  特别是我最棒的导师
God bless Rod and Todd and especially my wonderful mentor,
弗兰德斯先生
Mr. Flanders.
阿门
Amen.
我去帮大家拿干净的餐巾纸
Let me get fresh napkins for everyone.
怎么样呀
Hey, how's it going?
还是不敢相信你放弃了恶霸生涯
Still can't believe you've renounced the way of the bully.
我能说什么呢  人是会变的
Eh, what can I say? People change.
冻死你
Thaw-thaw!
再提醒我一遍  我为何放弃弗兰德斯选了你
Tell me again, why did I trade Flanders for you?
因为你能和我一起这样
Because we can do this.